<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-08-03T21:29:36-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">About Me</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/08/03/about-me.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About Me" /><published>2024-08-03T00:00:00-03:00</published><updated>2024-08-03T00:00:00-03:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/08/03/about-me</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/08/03/about-me.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hi! I’m Leonardo, but you can call me Leo.</p>

<p>With over 10 years of experience as a Software Engineer, I specialize in backend development for cloud-based applications. I possess a strong command of cloud services such as EC2, S3, Redshift, Step Functions, and RDS, along with languages like Go (Golang) and Python. I’m skilled in moving legacy applications to event-driven architectures.</p>

<p>I have a deep understanding designing and implementing data pipelines that transform raw data into high-quality, well-formatted datasets for analysis. Skilled in ETL processes to ensure data accuracy and usability.</p>

<p>My knowledge of the financial market industry includes experience with FX risks, Stocks Settlements, Fixed Income Products, and low-latency applications. I have a proven track record of designing, developing, and maintaining scalable, high-performance systems that meet the evolving needs of financial products.</p>

<p>Passionate about software development, I love staying up to date with the latest technologies and best practices. I’ve worked in companies from Brazil, Europe, and the USA, gaining valuable experience and knowledge. Let’s connect and share experiences.</p>]]></content><author><name>Leonardo Souza</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi! I’m Leonardo, but you can call me Leo.]]></summary></entry></feed>